question_data = [
    {
        "category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime & Manga",
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "question": "In the 1988 film &quot;Akira&quot;, Tetsuo ends up destroying Tokyo.",
        "correct_answer": "True",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "False"
        ]
    },
    {
        "category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime & Manga",
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "question": "Studio Ghibli is a Japanese animation studio responsible for the films &quot;Wolf Children&quot; and &quot;The Boy and the Beast&quot;.",
        "correct_answer": "False",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "True"
        ]
    },
    {
        "category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime & Manga",
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "question": "In Kill La Kill, the weapon of the main protagonist is a katana. ",
        "correct_answer": "False",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "True"
        ]
    },
    {
        "category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime & Manga",
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "question": "No Game No Life first aired in 2014.",
        "correct_answer": "True",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "False"
        ]
    },
    {
        "category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime & Manga",
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "question": "In the &quot;Melancholy of Haruhi Suzumiya&quot; series, the narrator goes by the nickname Kyon.",
        "correct_answer": "True",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "False"
        ]
    },
    {
        "category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime & Manga",
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "question": "In Pok&eacute;mon, Ash&#039;s Pikachu refuses to go into a pokeball.",
        "correct_answer": "True",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "False"
        ]
    },
    {
        "category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime & Manga",
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "question": "In the &quot;Toaru Kagaku no Railgun&quot; anime,  espers can only reach a maximum of level 6 in their abilities.",
        "correct_answer": "False",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "True"
        ]
    },
    {
        "category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime & Manga",
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "question": "Kiznaiver is an adaptation of a manga.",
        "correct_answer": "False",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "True"
        ]
    },
    {
        "category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime & Manga",
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "question": "In the &quot;To Love-Ru&quot; series, Golden Darkness is sent to kill Lala Deviluke.",
        "correct_answer": "False",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "True"
        ]
    },
    {
        "category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime & Manga",
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "question": "In Chobits, Hideki found Chii in his apartment.",
        "correct_answer": "False",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "True"
        ]
    }
]
